lovepanky.com 2019-08-29

# LovePanky Privacy Policy - LovePanky - Your Guide to Better Love and Relationships

**Privacy Policy**

At LovePanky (also known as LovePanky.com), we appreciate your readership and understand that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we respect the information you provide to us on our Website, and place a high interest in protecting this information. LovePanky is deeply committed to protecting your private information, but we would like to remind you that we are not responsible for the information available on websites linked to LovePanky and the privacy policies of websites that are linked to LovePanky.

Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. We also request you to understand and oblige with the LovePanky Privacy Policy, and acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy while using this Website.

**What does the LovePanky Privacy Policy cover?**

This policy discloses the privacy practices for LovePanky’s treatment of personal information that is gathered by LovePanky while you are on our Website and when you use our services. While our Privacy Policy does cover how we handle your information while browsing our Website, this policy does not apply to third parties that LovePanky does not employ or manage.

**What Personal Information does LovePanky collect?**

**Information that you provide to us**

LovePanky only collects personal information that you provide to us. We may store any information that you wilfully provide to us on our Website or in any other manner, including email interactions, etc., such as your name, email address, date of birth, gender, and other information that you choose to disclose to LovePanky based on your personal interest and requirements. You may choose to continue using our Website without providing the aforementioned information, by not registering to our Website. By not registering, you may lose out on advantages that may be provided to a registered member. The information you provide to LovePanky may be used to customize the advertising content that you may see, and also to provide you with a better experience while using our Website.

**Registration**

By registering to our Website, you may be provided with an advantage to receive periodic interactions by LovePanky, in the form of newsletters, promotional offers, polls, or other forms of communication that may be of interest to you. To avail this advantage, you will have to register at LovePanky and provide us with personal information. You may also opt out of receiving newsletters or any other third party promotions at any point in time.

**Comment Policy**

You must remember that you post comments on our Website at your own risk. We cannot guarantee that the information you post directly on the Website will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. You understand that copies of the information you have posted on the Website will be available, not only on the Website, but also in cached and archived pages or if other users or viewers of the Website have saved your information.

Once a comment is made public on the Website, it shall not be removed by request. As a user, you are responsible for your communication and for the consequences of the posting. Comments will be removed only in response to a legal process or in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or if LovePanky suspects that the comment is spam in nature, violates our terms of use, threatening to users of the Website, offensive to any community or race, or disturbs the public sentiments of users of the Website.

**Recording Information and Log Files**

LovePanky may receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. We automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, such as our cookie information, and similar data, but no “personal data” would be logged without your consent. We may also collect usage information such as number and frequency of visitors. We record these details to help diagnose problems with the system administration and servers, to analyze browsing trends and to gain information on how our Website is used by users, and to provide more interesting and informative content. We also use this information to customize advertisements, conduct researches, and to create reports for internal and external purposes such as marketing.

We use Google Analytics and Clicky Analytics to log and analyze the traffic to our website. You may review Clicky’s privacy policy at http://clicky.com/terms/privacy. A “Unique ID” tracking cookie is used for the “legitimate purpose” of identifying unique visitors, but otherwise no “personal data” is logged.

This information is not used to personally identify individuals or obtain personal information, but to provide better and relevant content, obtain information for advertising purposes and other purposes to better the Website, all of which does not include personal identification of users.

**Information about Cookies**

Our Website places an identifier known as a “cookie” on your computer’s hard drive. These are used through a web browser to enable us to recognize you whenever you visit us. Cookies are also used to customize your experience to help you have a better experience each time you visit LovePanky.

You can also deactivate or modify your cookies by modifying your browser preferences to accept cookies or reject them. But we recommend that you do not disable the cookies, as by rejecting LovePanky cookies, you may not be able to experience all of LovePanky’s available features and services.

Some of our affiliates or business partners may use cookies on our Website, such as advertisers. Such cookies allow advertising networks to receive information and deliver advertisements based on demographics or audiences, or any other segmentation they may prefer to use. These cookies used by LovePanky’s partners allow them to recognize your computer and compile information about the users of your computer. We do not have any access or control over these cookies used by our business partners, and this Privacy Policy does not cover their use of cookies.

We may use third party cookies from parties such as advertising companies when you visit our Website. This information may be used to obtain information about your visits to this site.

**Personalized Campaign’s Exclusion  **

If you prefer not to be a part of Lovepanky’s ongoing digital/marketing campaigns with advertising, you can go ahead and exercise your choice of opting out using the tool provided by the DAA or Digital Advertising Alliance in this link [here](http://optout.aboutads.info/).

**Children**

LovePanky caters to individuals who can legally create binding contracts. We take the protection of children’s privacy very seriously and comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and its accompanying FTC regulations, and we do not knowingly allow anyone under the age of 15 to provide us with personal information.

**Choice/Opt-out**

The users of this Website may be given the opportunity to “opt-in” to receive communications from LovePanky, either while registering or from time-to-time. You can decide to opt-in or opt-out as per your interest or requirement. If you decide to voluntarily opt-in to receive communication from us, you may receive information in the form of an email from LovePanky from time-to-time. Users who no longer wish to receive any communications from us may opt-out of receiving these communications by emailing contact@lovepanky.com with the subject line as “Unsubscribe”, or by following a link to unsubscribe that will be provided in every newsletter or subscribed email message from LovePanky.

**Delete Account**

You can edit or delete your account, if any, in the LovePanky Website by emailing us at contact@lovepanky.com with Account Information as the subject line.

**Changes in Privacy Policy**

If the privacy policy is changed, we will post the changes in this Privacy Policy page, or any other page we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of the information we collect and how we use it. If the changes in the Privacy Policy will affect the registered users, they will be notified via email or another mode of communication, and will have the option of deactivating their account if they do not comply with the changes. On the other hand, if we make any changes in the Privacy Policy that do not affect the user information that is already stored in our database, we will be posting the changes in this Privacy Policy page or put up a notice on the Website mentioning the change.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, you can contact us via email at contact@lovepanky.com.

Last Updated On: August 28, 2018
